《地球X的危机》前情回顾
Previously on "Crisis on Earth-X"...
-敬巴里和爱瑞丝  -敬巴里和爱瑞丝
- To Barry and Iris. - To Barry and Iris.
你真的在向我求婚吗
Are you asking me to marry you?
-我就是在求婚  -先别谈这件事了
- I am. - Just forget about it.
-费利西蒂  -我不想嫁给你
- Felicity. - I don't want to marry you!
我刚取消了订婚
I just called off my engagement.
祝烦心事走开
To making things go away.
在座各位有任何理由反对这对新人的结合吗
Does anyone have just cause why these two should not be married?
这是在逗我呢吧
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
纳粹
Nazis?
为什么纳粹想毁掉我的婚礼呢
Why would Nazis want to crash my wedding?
那是第53个地球  被称为地球X
There's a 53rd earth called Earth-X.
那也算是我们的地球  但有一个不同点
Basically our Earth with one difference.
纳粹打赢了战争
The Nazis won the war.
我称之为"火风暴之前的平静"
I call it "Calm After the Firestorm."
我们两个都不会有超能力了
No powers for either of us?
另一位弓箭手和会飞的女人
The other archer and flying woman
就是地球X上的奥利弗和卡拉
are Oliver and Kara of Earth-X,
斯旺在同他们合作
and Thawne is working with them.
将军快死了
The general is dying.
我们只需要一颗新心脏
All we need is a new heart.
我们找到了最佳捐赠者
And we found the perfect donor.
我觉得这不是我们的地球
I don't think this is our Earth.
免费工作场所
地球X
向前看
Eyes front!
这就是可怕的地球X了
So this crap-hole's Earth-X.
-威尔斯说得对  -他一般都对
- Wells was right. - He usually is.
难以想像这种鬼地方还真存在
It's hard to believe a place like this actually exists on any Earth.
我也赞同你的感受
I wish I shared your sentiment,
但是在我这么多次穿越时间中
but in all my travels to distant times,
唯一一件亘古不变的事情就是
one thing which sadly remains constant is men's ability
人与人之间的仇恨
to feel hatred for other men.
继续走
Keep moving.
快走
Move!
所有犯人  远离大门
All prisoners, stay away from the gate.
五角星和三角形
Stars and triangles...
用来标记这些人
Badges used to identify purported crimes
在这块土地上"犯"的所谓罪行
these people have "Committed" to land in here.
粉色三角形是什么意思
What's the pink triangle for?
你做了什么
What did you do?
我爱上了不该爱的人
I loved the wrong person.
我们得把这东西打开
We got to get out of these things.
-我们嬗变  -很乐意
- Transmute us out. - With pleasure.
我也无法震动出去
I can't vibrate through them either.
能量抑制环
Power-dampening collars.
那我们为什么要戴呢
Well, why are we wearing them, then?
无所谓了
Doesn't matter.
反正这里的守卫也很多
There's too many guards here anyways.
他们会杀了我妹妹
They're gonna kill my sister.
我们会阻止的
Look, we're not gonna let that happen,
艾丽克斯  我保证
Alex, I promise you.
我们得赶紧回到我们的地球上
We're gonna get back to our Earth before then.
怎么回  我们都不知道是怎么来的
How? We don't even know how we got here.
虽然我们不知道  但我们会弄明白的
No, we don't. We're gonna figure it out.
然后我们会找到离开这里的方法
Then we're gonna find a way to get out of this place,
回到我们爱的人身边
and we're gonna get back to the people we love.
希望其他人都没事
I hope everyone else is okay.
地球X危机  第三篇
地球一
里普·范·拉蒙终于醒了
Rip Van Ramon awakens.
这好像不是婚礼
This doesn't look like a wedding.
你错过了很多  西斯科
You missed quite a bit, Cisco.
你只需要知道你和我们一起
All you need to know is that you are locked
被关在了你这设计优良的
in one of your fabulous anti-meta-human cells
反超能力者牢房里
with the rest of us.
-我们逃不掉  -当然逃不掉
- We can't escape. - Of course we can't.
我当初就是这么设计的  天才
That's what I designed them for, genius.
真厉害
Good command of the obvious.
-各位  -那是球吗
- Boys. - Is that a ball?
这么了  吵到你了吗
Why? Is it bothering you?
是的
Yes.
天呐
God.
他们会一直这样吗
Are they gonna do that the whole time we're in here?
有可能
Probably.
-太烦了  停下  -停啥
- It hurts! Cut it out! - Cut what out?
尖端科研实验室
S.T.A.R. Labs.
就像以前一样  对吧
It feels like old times, doesn't it?
是我建造的这个地方
You know, I, I built this place...
凭我自己之力  十五年里
with my own hands and called it home
我都把这当作家  可你知道吗
for 15 years, and do you know what?
我并不喜欢待在这里
I hated every minute of it.
我的朋友们呢
Where are my friends?
你的朋友们  都在地球X上
Your friends, they're on Earth-X.
如果我是你的话  就不会太担心你的朋友们
I wouldn't worry about your friends too much because...
因为他们活不了多久了
they're not going to be alive much longer.
亲爱的
Oh, honey.
是因为红色阳光
It's because of the red sunlight.
相信我
And trust me,
它会让你虚弱到想像不到的地步
it'll make you weaker than you can possibly imagine.
你做这些  就是为了抓我吗
You did all this just...  just to get me?
你知道你们害死了多少无辜的人吗
Do you know how many innocent people you killed?
用他们的命换我的命
Their lives to save mine?
他们应该感到荣幸才是
Well, they should feel honored.
这是个很奇怪的感觉  对吧
It's a strange sensation, isn't it...
无能为力
feeling vulnerable?
而且  还会更糟
And it's just gonna get worse
因为这个红色日光
because this red sunlight,
能削弱你的力量
it's softening you up
然后很快
until pretty soon,
我就会像撬核桃一样把你大卸八块
I'm gonna crack you open like a walnut.
然后取走你那健全的心脏
Then I'm gonna take your healthy heart.
放进她体内
I'm gonna put it in her.
就是说我们应该能让你好起来
Which means we should probably get you going.
好
Good.
这样我就有时间和我自己
That'll give me time to talk to...
好好聊聊
myself.
听到了吗
Did you hear that?
其他人都在地球X上
Everyone else is on Earth-X.
还有几个小时  他们就会
And Kara only has a few hours
用门格勒的手法来对付卡拉
before they go full Mengele on her.
纳粹党卫队军官约瑟夫·门格勒
奥斯威辛集中营的医师"
执掌生杀大权并对囚犯进行人体试验
-我们要阻止他们  -你有办法吗
- We gotta stop them. - Got any ideas?
我不知道  给我点时间想想
I don't know. Give me some time to think.
爱瑞丝  我完全赞成女性当自强
Iris, I'm all for girl power and everything,
但我和你要怎么阻止我那更卑鄙
but how are you and I gonna stop the meaner, Nazi version
又纳粹版本的男友  管他现在是什么
of my whatever he is right now and...
还有那些有超能力的人
people with superpowers?
我们不必阻止他们
We don't have to.
我们只要去管道监狱  救出西斯科
We just need to get to the pipeline and get Cisco.
他就能关掉整栋楼的电力
He could turn off all the power to the building
打开缺口救我们出去
and breach us out of here.
你知道从这里怎么去管道监狱吗
Do you know how to get to the pipeline from here?
应该知道
I think so.
那带路吧  麦克莱恩
Lead the way, McClane.
快走
Move!
我不喜欢这种场面
I don't like the looks of this.
-出什么事了  -我不知道
- What's going on? - I don't know.
-继续走  -这是要干什么
- Keep moving! - What are we doing?
-到时间集合了  -集合什么
- It's roundup time. - Roundup for what?
快走
Move!
排好队
In line, now.
这些就是
So these are...
那些英雄吗
the heroes.
是的  党卫军少校
Yes, Sturmbannfuehrer.
金发
Blonde hair...
蓝眼  完美的北欧人
blue eyes-- this is Nordic perfection.
你为什么和这些杂种人结盟
Why would you align yourself with the unpure?
因为我喜欢男人
Because I like men
我还喜欢女人
and I like women.
以前我有个女儿  和你很像
You know, I had a daughter who looked just like you,
也有同样的冲动
with similar compulsions.
但是我把那小渣种
And I expunged that filth
从我的族谱上永远地抹去了
from my family line forever.
把他们带过来
Bring them all.
还有他
And him!
快走
Move! Now!
走
Go!
不是要大惊小怪  但如果我们没有逃脱计划
Not to be an alarmist, but if we don't have an escape plan,
我建议马上想一个
I suggest we get one immediately.
起来
Up!
走
Go.
转身
Turn around.
我知道你不是他
I know you are not him,
但我没法不在意你的脸
but I cannot stomach the sight regardless.
准备
Ready!
对不起  卡拉
I'm sorry, Kara.
瞄准
Aim!
我讨厌炮火
I hate "Fire."
史纳特
Snart?
你总算来了
About time!
杀光他们
Kill them all!
找掩护
Take cover!
你的时间掐得太紧了
Hey, you're cutting it close.
我觉得时间刚刚好
I thought that was great timing.
我真的很喜欢说双关语
I really enjoyed the pun.
你就是莱昂纳多·史纳特的二重身
So you're Leonard Snart's doppelganger.
不  我就是莱昂纳多·史纳
No, I'm Leonard Snart,
但你可以叫我莱奥
but you can call me Leo.
这套战衣真是太棒了
That is a fantastic outfit.
是你做的吗
Did you make that?
-莱奥  -对
- Leo. - Right.
是时候让你发光了  兄弟
Time to make you shine, buddy.
你
Uh, you, uh--
你们也许要闭上眼睛
you might want to close your eyes.
为什么
Why?
我想他刚回答了你的问题
Well, I believe he just answered your question.
来  我们走
Come on, let's go.
我们要去哪
Where are we going?
-去我们的基地  -你们的基地
- To our base. - Your base?
-你到底是谁  -我也在想同一个问题
- And-- and who are you? - I was thinking exactly
你们到底是谁
the same thing about you all.
你们也许得边走边说了
You might have to tell us on the way.
你越来越像人类了
You're looking more human.
害怕  无助  可悲  自卑
Scared, helpless, pathetic... inferior.
我们和他们没有什么不同
We're not that different from them.
拜托  他们就是想成为我们
Oh, please. We're everything they want to be:
金发  白皮肤
blonde, white.
完美的雅利安人
Aryan perfection.
我和你不一样
I'm not like you.
我认为我也没比其他人更好
I don't think I'm better than everyone else.
你不该这么想
You should.
你就是比他们好
You are.
你对他们来说就是神
You're a god to them.
你本来可以活得像神一样
You could have been living like one.
像你一样吗
Like you?
没错  像我一样
Yes, like me.
他们需要一个能俯首称臣的人
They want someone to bow to,
去崇拜  去领导
to worship, to lead.
你的所作所为不是领导
What you're doing is not leading.
是支配
It's ruling.
是的  没错
Yes, it is.
他们就是蝼蚁  卡拉
They're like ants, Kara.
他们不应该害怕我们的能力
They shouldn't fear us for what we can do.
他们应该在有需要是依靠我们
They should rely on us when they need us.
别跟我来这套乐善好施的鬼话
Oh, spare me the Good Samaritan crap.
我不会因为强大就去
I'm not gonna take advantage of anyone
利用其他人
just because I can.
保护弱者可不会让这个世界
The world isn't made better
变得更好
by protecting the weak.
除掉他们才会变得更好
It's made better by getting rid of them.
你真的是可怜
You really are pathetic.
你知道  我在婚礼上看到了你
You know, I saw you at the wedding.
自己一个人
By yourself.
可怜的  孤独的卡拉
Poor, lonely little Kara.
都找不到伙伴参加婚礼
Can't even find a date to a wedding.
你不知道你在说什么
You don't know what you're talking about.
这可都写在你这
It's written all over
发小脾气的脸上了
that pouty little face of yours.
你花费大部分时间在你的星球上
You spend so much time on your planet
照顾所有人  却忽视了你自己
taking care of everyone but yourself.
难怪你看起来这么的苦不堪言
No wonder you seem so utterly miserable.
没用的
It's not going to work.
你不会得到你想要的东西
You're not gonna get what you want.
真的吗
Really?
你为什么那么在乎我拿走你的心脏
Why do you care if I take your heart?
你又没有在用
You're not using it.
最起码我有一个
At least I have one.
快要好了
We're almost ready.
安全
Clear.
我知道坏人总是在不适当的时刻出现
I know bad guys have inopportune timing,
但是这一次  可真是最差的时刻了
but this is, like, the worst timing ever.
是啊  可不是吗
Yeah, tell me about it, sister.
巴里和我正准备结婚呢
Barry and I were just about to get married.
最起码你们分开时关系和睦
At least you guys left on good terms.
我和奥利弗最后说的话是
The last thing I said to Oliver was,
"我不想嫁给你"
"I don't want to marry you,"
然后他现在被困在了纳粹世界
And now he's stuck in Nazi world.
如果咱们再也见不到他们怎么办
I mean, what if we never see them again?
站住
Stop!
举起手来
Hands in the air!
真是太厉害了
That was extremely badass.
你也是
Same to you.
西斯科
Cisco.
Cisco?
各位  我们被困在这里了
Guys, we're trapped in here!
我们会放你出来的
We're gonna get you of here!
液压过低
你这是在逗我呢吗
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
-怎么了  -我打不开防爆门
- What? - I can't open the blast door.
你是说他们被困住了
You mean they're trapped?
我给传奇们发送求救信号
I'll send an SOS to the Legends.
要多久他们才能接受到
How long will it take for them to get it?
要看他们在哪个时间段里了
Depends where they are in time.
咱们等不了那么久
We can't wait that long.
求救信号
只能咱们来救卡拉了
It's up to us to save Kara.
我想咱们是在地球X的星城
I guess we're in Earth-X's Star City.
不得不说  你们的故事真奇特
I have to say, that's one hell of a story.
-你是个极速者  -对
- You're a speedster. - Yeah.
好吧  你俩可以变成燃烧的火人
Okay, you two turn into the burning man.
没错
Yup.
而你是元首的好人二重身
And you're the good doppelganger of the Fuehrer.
"好人"这个描述可能有些过于简化了
"Good" Might be an oversimplification.
你还没告诉我们你是哪个地球来的呢
You still haven't told us which Earth you're from.
显然不是这里的
Clearly, it's not this one.
我们是地球一来的
We're from Earth-1.
地球一  真是...
Earth-1? Well...
巧了
golly.
我是漏掉了什么吗
Am I missing something here?
我也是地球一来的
I'm from Earth-1 too.
如果你是我们地球来的
If you're from our Earth,
那你一定知道我们怎么来这里的  对吗
then you know how we got here, don't you?
是  我大概清楚是怎么回事
Yeah, I have a pretty good idea.
我想你们...
I think you guys...
是通过这个来的
came through this.
-一个临时通道  -与裂口一样的原理
- A temporal gateway? - Same physics as a breach,
-只不过更大更稳定  -是  大多了
- just more stable and larger. - Yeah, much larger.
所以我们有了回去的方法
So we have a way to get back.
那这个东西在哪
So where is this thing?
其实离这里并不远
It's actually not too far from here.
准确来说是两万二千三百米远
22.3 kilometers, to be exact.
-我们可以开车过去  -很好
- Well, we'd drive there. - Good.
那就带我们去
So take us to it.
-不能这么做  -为什么
- Can't do that. - Why?
因为通道所处的建筑被
Because the gateway's in a facility guarded
一个不那么小的纳粹军队守卫着
by a not-so-small army of Nazis.
我们面对过更糟的情况  所以...
Yeah, well, we've faced worse, so...
那是我们唯一回家的路
Look, it's our only way home.
我们去定了
We're going through it.
你们哪也去不了
Nobody's going through anything.
因为我们要炸掉它
Because we're blowing it the hell up.
温
Winn?
-请叫自由斗士肖特将军  -肖特将军
- Please, Freedom Fighter General Schott. - General Schott?
是  你又是谁
Yeah, and who are you?
地球一来的新朋友
New friends from Earth-1.
他们是咱们这一边的
They're on our side.
除了你们想要
Except for the part where you guys
把我们唯一的回家路炸毁
want to blow up our only way home.
其实我们也不想
We don't exactly want to.
我们关心的所有人都在
Everyone we care about is on the other side
门的另一边  被纳粹囚禁了
of that gateway, imprisoned by Nazis.
纳粹想要把我妹妹剖开
The Nazis that want to cut open my sister.
-我们得回去  -摧毁设备
- We have to get back. - Eliminate that facility,
你们就毁了我们从你们敌人手上
and you eliminate our only chance
拯救朋友的唯一机会
of saving our friends from your enemies.
抱歉  不过这个机会我们
I'm sorry, but we've been waiting
等了很多年
for an opportunity like this for years.
不能继续等下去了
We cannot wait any longer.
这是我们唯一可以
This is our only chance
让元首和他的军队分开的机会
to separate the Fuehrer from his army.
我们试着扭转战局
We are trying to turn this war around.
你们准备把我们的地球给三个疯子摆布
You are gonna leave our Earth at the mercy
而他们曾破坏过你们的地球
of the three psychopaths who have ravaged yours.
等等  为什么这个人
Wait, why does this man look exactly
和我想要杀的元首那么像
like the Fuehrer I am trying to kill?
无指手套男  我们想要的
Look, fingerless gloves, all we are asking
只是一点时间
is for a little bit of time.
让我们进入装置  通过那扇门
Let us get into the facility and through that gateway.
那道门被30辆12型装甲车
The gateway is guarded by 30 Panzer XIIs,
50辆突击虎  100名纳粹党卫军把守
50 Sturmtigers, and 100 Schutzstaffel officers.
-也许不是最好的机会  -我会试试
- Not the best odds, maybe. - I'll take them.
不行
No, you will not.
我们马上就要炸了那扇门
We are blowing up that gateway right now.
最后的命令
Final order.
抱歉他说话比较粗鲁
Sorry he's a little rough around the edges.
但他是将军  所以发号施令
But he is the general, and he's issued his commands.
等等
Hey, hey, hey.
你改不了他的主意  没人可以
You won't change his mind. No one does.
在我的地球上  我和他像是一家人
Look, on my Earth, he and I are like family.
为了帮我妹妹他什么都愿意做
And he would do anything to help my sister.
雷  随她去
Ray, let her try.
你看上去不知道如何接受指令
You don't seem to know how to take an order.
因为我习惯于发号施令
That's because I'm used to giving them.
你不能这么做  温
You can't do this, Winn.
我是肖特将军
General Schott.
我不知道你觉得你是在哪里
Look, I don't know where the hell you think you are,
但这个星球在战争中过了太多年代
but this planet has been at war for generations.
我们累了
We are tired.
很多人的死因
There are men dying
甚至和他们的祖父是一样的
for the same causes their grandfathers did.
我们不是让你们投降
We're not asking you to surrender.
只是你毁了那东西之前
Hey, just--just let us get back home
让我们先回家
before you destroy that thing.
我只是想争取一点时间
I-I'm just asking for a little time.
时间就是我无法给你的
Time is what I can't give you.
他们有一种武器
They have a weapon...
那种末日武器威力巨大
a doomsday weapon powerful enough
足够影响其他世界
to affect other worlds.
它必须被毁灭
It has to be eliminated.
温
Winn.
拜托
Please.
你地球上的元首
The Fuehrer on your Earth,
你憎恨的人们
the people that you hate,
他们要杀了我妹妹
they're going to kill my sister
如果你不让我回去救她
if you don't let me get back to save her.
我所在的地球上  我妹妹是你的闺蜜
On my Earth, my sister is your closest friend.
她救了你太多次
She's saved you countless times.
你愿意付出一切帮助她
You would do anything to help her.
你们为帮助对方不计代价
You would do anything to help each other,
不管多大的危险  毫无疑问
no matter the risk, without question.
所以我向你讨一个机会
So all I'm asking for is a chance.
拜托
Please.
对你妹妹的遭遇
I am sorry about your sister
和你的地球我深表遗憾
and about your Earth.
真的
I truly am.
但今天我有机会
But today I have the chance
保护我的人
to protect my people,
我的地球
my Earth.
我决心已定
My decision stands.
温
Winn.
杰佛逊
Jefferson?
灰老头  我在忙呢
Grey, I'm busy, man.
我看到了  但我希望
Yes, I can see that, but I was hoping
你能从你对反乌托邦另类历史的沉思中
you might take a moment away from your ruminations
抽出些时间  接受我的道歉
on dystopian alternative history to accept my apology.
我可能是个有学问的人
I may be a learned man,
但我不总是一个聪明人
but I am not always an astute one.
我觉得我对于
I think I was just so thrilled
迫近的离开机会太兴奋了
with the reality of my imminent departure
以至于忽略了你的感受
that I neglected to consider your feelings.
我并不想要让你和你的家人
Look, man, I'm not trying to take you away from your family
-分离什么的  -你就是我的家人
- or nothing-- - You are my family.
很久以前  我出乎意料地有了个女儿
Long before I unexpectedly found myself with a daughter,
后来出乎意料地有了儿子
I found myself unexpectedly with a son.
-我明白  我只是...  -你明白
- Yeah, I know. I ju-- - You know.
你明白吗
You know, do you?
环顾四周  我们现在在
Look around you. We're standing in one of the...
能够想像到的最黑暗的地方之一
darkest places imaginable.
我却有些乐观  知道为什么吗
Yet somehow I'm optimistic. Do you know why?
因为你是个疯狂的老头
'Cause you're a crazy old man.
对  不是
Yes. No!
因为我身边有你
Because I'm standing here with you.
我从未想过自己能有这么棒的儿子
You are a better son than I could have ever hoped for.
时间的推移或多远的距离
And no length of time or distance
都没法改变这一点
will ever change that.
好吧  原谅你了  来
A'ight. Apology accepted. Come here.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
找一把枪
Looking for a gun...
或是一把刀  什么都行
or knife--anything.
我不管他们有多少台突击虎
Okay, I don't care how many Sturmtigers they have out there.
我要去救卡拉
I'm gonna go save Kara,
这些人帮不帮忙我都要去
with or without the help of these people.
你不能去
No, you're not.
我是有着三十多种
I'm a government agent
军用武器执照的政府特工
certified in over 30 military weapons.
你很厉害  我认同
And you're impressive, I'll give you that.
但你还是没法孤身一人
But you still can't fight your way
心惊胆战地从纳粹军中杀出一条路
through an army of Nazis alone and scared.
我没有心惊胆战
I'm not scared.
不是为你自己  是为你妹妹
No, not for you. For your sister.
我本该做更多的
I should've done more.
要是我没有这么...分心的话
I mean, if I hadn't gotten so...distracted.
真抱歉让你分心了
Well, sorry to be a distraction.
你不明白
You don't understand.
我不能失去她
I can't lose her.
我比你认为的更明白
I understand more than you think.
我失去了我的妹妹
I lost my sister.
我因不能救下她
The anger and guilt that I felt
内心所产生的愤怒和愧疚
for not being able to save her
让我走上了黑暗的道路
took me down a dark path.
抱歉  我不知道这事
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
你又怎么能知道呢
How could you?
我们唯一了解彼此的就是...
I mean, the only thing we know about each other is...
对方不穿衣服的样子
what we look like with clothes off.
顺便说一下  你很美
Beautiful, by the way.
你还不知道我会保护我的团队
You also don't know that I protect my team,
而你  丹弗斯  也是我团队的一员
and you, Danvers, you're on my team.
我向你保证  我们不会让
And I promise you, we're not gonna let
我妹妹发生的事在你妹妹身上重演
what happened to my sister happen to yours.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我只是想...我想救卡拉
I just want to-- I want to save Kara,
我还想回到玛吉的身边
and I want to get back to Maggie.
-玛吉是谁  -很复杂
- Maggie is? - Complicated.
是啊  我也有过一位玛吉
Yeah. I had a Maggie too.
我一直都想回到她身边
And I think about going back to her...
无时无刻不想
all the time.
听着  艾丽克斯
Look, Alex.
你看起来是个周到的人
You seem like a pretty thoughtful person.
如果你觉得某些事行不通
And if you thought it wasn't gonna work out
必须要终止
and had to end it,
我相信你有个合理的理由
I'm sure that reason was valid.
相信你的直觉
Trust your instincts.
雷  求你了  我们跟他谈谈吧
Ray, please, let's talk to him.
听着  是你说让艾丽克斯试试的
Look, you said to let Alex try.
我让她试了
I let her try.
-而她没有成功  -那就这样了吗
- She didn't succeed. - So that's that?
我们就让这些穿着奇装异服的可怜人
We just let these poor strangely dressed individuals
失去唯一回家的路吗
lose their one way home?
这是温的命令
Look, it's what Winn ordered,
不管在哪个地球上我都没有违抗将军的习惯
and I am not in the habit of defying generals on any Earth.
那你在地球一的家人呢
And what about your family back on Earth-1?
他们怎么了
What about them?
你可能有机会再见到他们
You'd be giving up any chance of ever seeing them again.
莱奥
Leo...
你为什么这么急切
why are you pushing this?
-你说什么  -我们为这场战争
- Pardon? - We have fought
奋战  流血  牺牲
and bled and sacrificed for this war.
这些陌生人一出现
And then these strangers show up
你就愿意为了他们抛弃一切吗
and you're willing to throw everything away for them?
世界的命运危在旦夕
The fate of the world is at stake.
他们所爱之人的性命也危在旦夕
So are the lives of their loved ones.
得了吧
Come on.
随你怎么嘲笑我多愁善感
Tease me all you want for being sentimental.
这些英雄会为了他们所爱的人
These heroes would risk everything
冒牺牲一切的风险  我也是如此
for the people they love, just like I would...
为了你
for you.
你知道你这么看着我的时候
You know I can't say no
我没有办法拒绝
when you look at me like that.
所以我才这样看着你
That is why I look at you like that.
我们与将军谈过了  在争论了许久后
We talked to the general, and after a lot of arguing,
-他同意了  所以...  -我们会帮你
- he agreed, so... - We're gonna help you out.
你提到了一百名守卫
Now, you referenced 100 guards.
那么他们大多数人都是在周围活动吗
I assume most of them are around the perimeter?
-对  -好的
- Correct. - All right.
我们突击出去
We fight through them outside.
进入主走廊
We access the main corridor.
机库里面的警备如何
What is security like inside the hangar?
我去侦查一下
I'll do some recon.
整个设施
So the entire facility
都有超能力者阻尼器
has meta-human dampeners.
好吧  我们没法不用超能力就拿下机库
Okay, we can't take that hangar with no powers, man.
从那些卫星看出  机库外有个控制室
These satellites indicate a control room off the hangar.
阻尼器肯定是在那里
That must be where the dampener is.
好吧  我们肯定没法不用超能力
Okay, well, we definitely can't take
就拿下主控制室
the main control room with no powers.
咱们又不能混入里边去
It's not like we blend in here.
我想我知道该怎么进去了
I think I know how to get in.
我违背了自己的判断力  同意了这次行动
I'm allowing this mission against my better judgment.
你只有一小时
You have one hour.
我很感激你  我们都是
I appreciate it. We all do.
我知道  我知道你在想什么
Yeah, I know. I know what you're thinking.
要是你没能穿过通道
If you don't make it through the gateway,
我不会给你更多时间的
I am not giving you more time.
我会把那里炸上天
I will blow that place to kingdom come.
红色光线饱和度
Red light saturation...
已经彻底浸透
is complete.
她准备好了
She's cooked.
醒来之后你会变得前所未有的强大
And you will wake up stronger than you've ever been.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
很不幸  丹弗斯小姐
Unfortunately, Miss Danvers,
手术过程中你需要保持清醒
we need you awake for this procedure.
我表哥...
My--my cousin...
会找到你的
he'll find you.
你表哥
Your cousin.
真的吗  告诉你件事
Really? Fun tidbit.
我和他打过一架  未来某个时候
I fought your cousin once. In the future.
他确实很快
He is fast.
但我更快
I'm faster.
他们开始手术了
They're starting the surgery.
我在努力了  马上...
I'm working on it, and...
只靠备用电源做不了手术
Just have backup power, and it's not enough.
我们审查过这里的每一个人
Well, everyone in the building has been accounted for.
他们能藏在哪儿
Where might people be hiding?
尝尝这个  纳粹杂种
Take that you Nazi mother.
想活着就跟我走
Come with me if you want to live.
我需要阳光
Get me to the sun.
好好  好的
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay.
-我扶她  我扶她  -好
- I got her, I got her. - Okay.
我们得走了
We gotta go.
我想斯旺先生没有同意你们离开
I don't believe Mr. Thawne is done with you yet.
请出示证件  士兵
Your papers, Sturmmann.
我们没有证件
We don't have papers.
这是特别访问
This is a special visit.
证件  马上
Your papers. Now.
随便你  不过...
Suit yourself, but...
你还是和我老板说吧
I think you better talk to our boss.
不用动
As you were.
我的天  抱歉长官
Mein gott. My apologies, sir.
快放行
Let them through!
放行
谢谢您  元首先生
Thank you, mein Fuehrer.
元首先生  我们...
Mein Fuehrer, we were
没想到您会来
we were not expecting you.
我也没想到这么快就回来
Nor was I anticipating being back so soon.
因为你的无能
Thanks to your incompetence,
地球一的二重身...
the Earth-1 doppelgangers...
我的二重身
My doppelganger...
逃走了
Escaped his execution.
是的  他逃走了
Yes, he did.
然后呢
And?
我们正全力以赴寻找他们
We are exhausting every possible means to locate them.
很好
Good.
您想让我们因此延迟部署吗
Would you like us to delay deployment until we do so?
什么部署
Deployment?
她已经准备好了
She is inbound and ready.
末日装置
The doomsday device.
冲浪者已全面启动
The Wellenreiter is fully operational
一切准备就绪  元首先生
and at the ready, mein Fuehrer.
要把她送过去吗
Shall we send her through?
按计划进行
As scheduled.
开始
Begin!
冲浪者已经上路
The Wellenreiter is on its way.
胜利万岁
Hail, victory!
Hail, victory.
-报告  -好消息
- Report. - Good news.
冲浪者就要到这个地球了
The Wellenreiter's made the transition to this Earth.
卡拉是最重要的
Kara is all that matters.
我们用来照射她的那个红色阳光
That red sunlight we're flooding her with,
已经快耗尽了
that's burning off.
很快  她的细胞就不再饱和
So pretty soon, her cells will be so desaturated,
我们就没法进行手术了
we cannot perform the surgery.
-修好  -做不到
- Fix it. - I can't.
这是你的城市  你的设施
This is your city. This is your facility.
把电源恢复
So turn the power back on.
做不到  因为系统被加密了
I can't because the system has been encrypted.
谁加密的
By who?
斯莫克小姐
By Miss Smoak.
还有什么可以为您效劳的吗
Is there anything else I can help you with?
不用了
No, that'll be all.
好的
Very well.
临走之前有件东西要给您  元首先生
Before I go, I have something for you, mein Fuehrer.
一份礼物
A gift...
庆祝您的回归
to celebrate your return.
警卫
Guard!
我知道您很喜欢惩罚不守规矩的人
Well, I know how much you enjoy executing rule breakers,
她可坏了不少规矩
and this one has broken many of them.
我们发现这个犹太女人
We discovered this Jewess
把她的口粮让给了劳动营的孩子
handing her rations to the work camp children.
完全违反了营地的规定
Strictly against camp rules, of course.
那些孩子快饿死了
Those children were starving.
这一定很艰难
Well, this must be hard.
听说您在地球一的二重身
I hear your doppelganger on Earth-1
爱过一个和她长得一样的女人
loved a woman who looks just like this.
你觉得我会不验证你的身份
Did you really think I would hand you a loaded weapon
就把装了子弹的手枪给你吗
Before verifying who you are?
好了  好了
Hey, hey, hey, you're okay.
你没事的  没事的
No, no, no, you're fine. You're fine.
拿着这个  快走
Just take this and go.
为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
强者应当保护弱者
It's the strong's duty to protect the weak.
拿着枪快走
Take it and go.
走
Go!
安全
Clear.
怎么会...
How did it...
巴里  有麻烦了
Barry, we have a problem.
通道控制已被毁
The gateway control's been damaged.
打不开吗
We can't turn it on?
从这里打不开
We can't turn it on here,
但平台上应该可以手动超控
but there should be a manual override at the platform.
好  那我们就杀出一条血路
All right, we're gonna have to fight our way through.
什么意思  召回
What do you mean? Call it back!
来不及了  已经编程好了
Too late. It's been programmed.
现在无法改变航线
There's no changing course now.
你说给我们一小时
You said we'd have an hour.
对  但我改变主意了
Yeah, well, I changed my mind.
小队还没穿过缺口
The team hasn't gone through the breach yet.
那支队伍跟我们以及拯救我们的星球无关
That team has nothing to do with us or saving our planet.
真正有威胁的
And everyone who can threaten it
是缺口另一边的人
is on the other side of that breach.
不能让他们回来
They are not coming back through.
-将军  -莱昂  够了
- General! - Leo, enough!
我不会再浪费时间
I'm not risking any more time.
这缺口炸定了
We are blowing it up.
各位  有麻烦了
Guys, we have a problem.
什么麻烦
What kind of problem?
有武器要炸毁这处设施
A weapon is heading to blow up the facility.
武器  是导弹吗
A weapon? You mean a missile?
也不算
Not exactly.
费利西蒂·斯莫克
Felicity Smoak.
重新接通电源
Turn the power back on.
他说
He said...
费利西蒂
Felicity!
"重新接通电源"
"Turn the power back on."
抱歉  艾尔伯德  艾尔伯德
Sorry, Eobard. Eobard?
-艾尔伯德  -艾尔伯德
- Eobard. - Eobard.
天啊  未来真奇怪
My God, the future sounds weird.
有意思
That's funny.
有时我们会高估自己的聪明才智
Sometimes we think we're more clever than we are.
因为我所在的时代
Because where I come from,
历史书上写满了
the history books are filled with stories
这个英雄时代的故事
of this Age of Heroes:
绿箭侠
Green Arrow,
黑金丝雀
Black Canary,
闪电侠
The Flash.
然而
And yet no one...
从来没人听说过
no one has ever heard
费利西蒂·斯莫克
of Felicity Smoak.
住手
Stop!
住手  住手
Stop. Stop.
你是冲我来的  那就带我走吧
You came here for me, so just take me, please.
求你别伤害其他人
Please don't hurt anyone else.
告诉他们代码
Give them the code.
-我要是说了  他们会杀了你  -没事
- If I do, they'll kill you. - It's fine.
不能有人为我而死
Nobody's gonna die because of me.
拿铁  艾达  乔纳斯  11900
Latte, Ada, Jonas, 1-1-9-0-0.
拿铁
Latte?
可爱
Cute.
系统锁定
走
Let's go.
十分钟后  红色龙卷风
In ten minutes, Red Tornado's
会摧毁整座设施
gonna bring down this entire facility,
而我们无法阻止那个机器人
and there's nothing we can do to stop that robot.
在那之前
Then we need to reopen the gateway
我们得重新打开通道
before that happens.
-巴里  雷  -我们知道
- Barry, Ray-- - We know.
想办法阻止某个会飞的机器人
Stop a flying robot somehow.
好  其他人负责打开缺口
Good. The rest of us will open the breach.
计划就这些吗
That's the whole plan?
我们认识的史纳特经常说
Well, as a Snart we know used to say,
"制定计划  实施计划
"Make a plan. Execute the plan.
料到计划会出岔子
Expect the plan to go off the rails.
抛弃计划"
Throw away the plan""
真是...烂透了的建议
Wow. That is... that is terrible advice.
我总会制定计划  缜密可靠
I always have a plan, down to the second,
所以从没出过岔子
so nothing ever goes wrong.
不不不  现在唯一的计划
No, no, no, the only plan now
就是别抛下我离开这地球
is not to leave this Earth... without me.
好
Okay.
好  准备好追逐龙卷风了吗
Right. Ready for Tornado watch.
开始吧
Let's do it.
我们穿上战衣才有意思
I thought it'd be fun if we put on our costumes.
你从哪搞到的弓和箭袋
Where'd you get the bow and quiver?
将军爱搜藏武器
The general collects weapons.
上战场吧
Let's go to war.
谁都别想靠近通道
No one gets to the gateway!
谁都别想
No one!
走  走
Move! Move!
来了
Here we go.
好  纳粹全干掉了  走
Okay, we're Nazi-free. Let's go.
等等  那是一枚自动超能电池
Hold on. That's an automated power cell.
在用控制台之前得激活它
We need to activate it before using the control console.
我可以热线启动  没问题
I can hot-wire it, no problem.
那我去启动控制台
Then I'll turn on the console.
你想分头行动  确定吗
You want to split up? You sure?
这样胜算最大
It's our most favorable odds.
给他们点颜色瞧瞧  杰佛逊
Let's kick some ass, Jefferson.
灰老头  电源连好了
Grey, we got power.
雷
Ray!
帮帮忙
A little help here!
糟糕
Oh, crap.
这样不太公平
Well, that's not very fair.
我被困住了
I'm pinned down!
灰老头  不
Gray! No!